A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Tech Review Panel, 2007-2009 (bulk 2007)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Files of Virginia Tech Review Panel Members, 2007-2009., Extent: 1.94 cubic feet (7 boxes) and 999 emails. (Box 1-4 and 58-60)
  - Series I. Files of Virginia Tech Review Panel Members, Subseries B. Records of Diane Strickland, 2007., Extent: 0.98 cu. ft. (boxes 2-4) and 256 emails
    - Seung-Hui Cho's health records from Virginia Tech's Schiffert Health Center and Cook Counseling Center, 12 June 2007 (date transmitted). (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Seung-Hui Cho's education records from Virginia Tech, 29 June 2007 (date transmitted). (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Seung-Hui Cho's education records from Virginia Tech, 29 June 2007 (date transmitted). (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Seung-Hui Cho's education records from Fairfax County Public Schools, 3 July 2007 (date transmitted). (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Seung-Hui Cho's medical records from Carilion New River Valley Medical Center and Carilion Saint Alban's Behavioral Health, 6 July 2007 (date transmitted). (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, May-July 2007. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Tech Review Panel Report outline/drafts, June-August 2007. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Treatment Advocacy Center material, 17 July 2007. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Treatment Advocacy Center material, 17 July 2007. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Department of Justice, Office for Victims of Crime publications, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Department of Justice, Office for Victims of Crime DVDs, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, undated. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fatal School Shootings in the United States, 1966-2007, prepared by Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher LLP, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Series I. Files of Virginia Tech Review Panel Members, Subseries C. Records of Carroll Ann Ellis, April to September 2007., Extent: 226 emails
    This subseries contains 226 emails sent and received by Carroll Ann Ellis between April and September 2007 that can be accessed online. Ellis was the Director of the Fairfax County Police Department's Victim Services Division, a faculty member at the National Victim Academy, and a member of the American Society of Victimology. There are 13 confidential emails that are restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Restricted material includes privileged records (attorney-client communications and attorney work product). Ellis' unrestricted email is accessible online.
    Email subjects include: media stories on the shooting, work of the Panel, and release of Panel report; Panel meetings; writing of report, including concerns about reviewing drafts and finishing work by 23 August 2007; and interviews (proposed lists and notes).
    Notable email includes: email from Gerald Massengill, dated 9 July 2007, to Roger Depue and Phil Schaenman, on law enforcement response at Virginia Tech; email from Gordon Davies, dated 1 July 2007, to panel and Phil Schaenman and Hollis Stambaugh, sharing his thoughts on how to frame the Panel's report; email from Daryl Sensenig, dated 29 May 2007, to Ellis, containing notes from 25 May 2007 interview of Dr. Marcella Fierro, Virginia State Medical Examiner; email from Hollis Stambaugh, dated 11 June 2007, to the Panel forwarding a letter from John Hammaren, father of Caitlin Hammaren; and email from Phil Schaenman, dated 27 June 2007, to Panel containing a first draft of a comprehensive outline for the Panel report including assignments for Panel members.
    Email correspondents include: Richard Brusca, Teresa Coping, Gordon Davies, Roger Depue, Jim Kudla, Marcus Martin, Gerald Massengill, Lenwood McCoy, Phil Schaenman, Amy Sabrin, Bela Sood, Hollis Stambaugh, and Diane Strickland.
  - Series I. Files of Virginia Tech Review Panel Members, Subseries D. Records of Gerald Massengill, April to September 2007., Extent: 105 emails
    This subseries contains 105 emails send and received by Gerald Massengill between April and September 2007 that can be accessed online. Massengill, Panel Chair, was a retired Virginia State Police Superintendent who led the Commonwealth's law enforcement response to the 11 September 2001, attack on the Pentagon and the sniper attacks that affected the Commonwealth in 2002. There is one confidential email that is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Restricted material includes privileged records (attorney-client communications and attorney work product). Massengill's unrestricted email is accessible online.
    Email subjects include: media stories on the shooting, work of the Panel, and release of Panel report; interviews by Panel member and staff; and media interviews.
    Notable email includes: email from Roger Depue, dated 18 June 2007, to Massengill sharing a contact Depue had with Eric and Beth Hilshire, parents of Emily Hilshire; email exchange with Roger Depue, dated 11-12 August 2007, in which he discusses his review of Cho's writings at State Police Headquarters in Salem and his discussion with the Special Agent Chuck Eaton; email from Massengill, dated 28 August 2007, to Phil Schaenman, relaying his conversation with Virginia Tech Police Chief Wendell Flinchum regarding bomb threats on campus; email from Massengill, dated 6 July 2007, to Hollis Stambaugh, Richard Brusca, and Phil Schaenman, about Cho's gun purchases; and email exchange between Massengill and Schaenman, dated 23 August 2007, about Cho's cell phone records.
    Email correspondents include: Roger Depue, Jim Kudla, Larry Roberts, Phil Schaenman, and Hollis Stambaugh.
- Series II. Files of TriData, a Division of System Planning Corporation, 2007., Extent: 5.78 cubic feet (17 boxes) and 1766 emails. (Box 5-21)
  The Files of TriData series documents the collection of materials for and the writing and editing of the Panel's report to Governor Kaine. Series is arranged into three subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Drafts of M ass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 2007; B. Confidential Seung Hui Cho Documents, 2007; C. Collected Documents Related to the Investigation, 2007. This collection includes health records, legal advice, and personal information that are restricted for 75 years by the Code of Virginia (Virginia Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act, Virginia Public Records Act, Virginia Health Records Privacy Act). Restricted documents have been sealed but have not been removed from the collection.
  TriData, a division of Arlington based System Planning Corporation, provided staff support for the Virginia Tech Review Panel. In April 2007, Col. Gerald Massengill, Chairman of the Virginia Tech Review Panel, requested that Governor Tim Kaine on behalf of the Commonwealth retain TriData to assist the Panel in completing an independent analysis of the circumstances of the 16 April 2007 shooting at Virginia Tech. TriData provided research, staff support and logistics for the Panel. TriData assisted the Panel in collecting, organizing, and analyzing relevant information needed to develop a detailed factually analysis of the shooting, and the preparation of the Panel's report and recommendations to Governor Kaine.
  In August 2009, Governor Kaine retained TriData again to correct errors and update the original report. The Addendum was released in November 2009 and revised in December 2009.
  TriData staff that assisted the Panel included: Philip Schaenman, panel staff director; Hollis Stambaugh, panel staff deputy director; Jim Kudla, panel public information officer; Dr. Harold Cohen; Darryl Sensenig; Paul Flippin; Teresa Copping; Maria Argabright; Shania Flagg; Lucius Lamar III; Rachel Merson; and Jim Gray.
  - Series II. Files of TriData, Subseries A. Drafts of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 2007., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (boxes 5-8)
    This subseries contains multiple drafts of chapters of the Virginia Tech Panel's final report to Governor Kaine. The records include comments and edits by members of the Virginia Tech Review Panel, TriData, and Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher and Flom LLP, the law firm advising the panel. Some but not all drafts are dated and indicate the person who made the comments/edits. Some drafts indicate the date when the edits/comments were added to the documents by TriData staff (usually by Shania Flagg). The chapter numbers and titles changed during the writing of the report and may not necessarily correspond to the chapters in the final report. This subseries contains attorney-client privileged records. Restricted documents have been sealed but have not been removed from the collection.
    - Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, completed 26 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, completed 21-23 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, with changes probably made by Lucius Lamar, 22 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft of Appendices, 18 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Draft of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 18 August 2007. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine (Philip Schaenman Master Copy), 17 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Partial Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, undated. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Partial Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 18 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Partial Draft Report of Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Report of the Virginia Tech Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 15-17 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Partial Draft Mass Shootings at Virginia Tech, April 16, 2007: Preliminary Report of the Review Panel presented to Governor Kaine, 31 July-2 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Drafts, Multiple Chapters, with edits/comments by Tom Ridge, undated. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Tentative Report Outline, 16 July 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Executive Summary, undated. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Executive Summary, with edits/comments by Skadden, 22 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Summary of Key Findings, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 27 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Executive Summary, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 22 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Dedication, 15 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Acknowledgements, 20 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Acknowledgements, 27 August 2007, 6:00 p.m. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Acknowledgements, 27 August 2007, 4:30 p.m. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Acknowledgements, 27 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Introduction, 7 July 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Introduction, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, undated. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chapter I. Introduction, last changed 23 July 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chapter I. Introduction (first page), last changed 23 July 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Introduction, 7 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Introduction, 8 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chapter I. Background and Scope, 9 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 10 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 9 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, 9 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, 17 August 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter I. Background and Scope, with edits/comments by Hollis Stambaugh, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Chapter II. University Setting and Security, undated. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. University Setting and Security, 15 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 30 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 30 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 31 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 2 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Tom Ridge, 3 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Amy Sabrin, 8 August 2007 [RESTRICTED]. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Carroll Ann Ellis, 10 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 10 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security (selected pages), with edits by Skadden, 22 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 22 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. University Setting and Security, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, undated. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. Virginia Tech Shooting Timeline, 19 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, 6 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 6 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter II. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Brad Marcus, 8 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 8 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Chapter III. Timeline of Events, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 10 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, 14 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 22 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter III. Timeline of Events, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Interview Notes of Bela Sood (Cho's history), July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IV. Mental Health History of Seung Hui Cho, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Information Privacy Law, prepared by Skadden, 2 August 2007 [RESTRICTED]. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IV.A. Information Privacy Laws and Confusion Surrounding Them, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Information Privacy Laws, suggested edits by Michael Tierney, 6 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Information Privacy Laws: Their Misapprehension, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Information Privacy Laws: Their Misapprehension, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, Diane Strickland, Gerald Massengill, Tom Ridge, and Marcus Martin, 6 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 6 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Guns-Law, 7 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, 10 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Policies, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 11 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Policies, 11 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Policies, 11 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Policies, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 12 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter V. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 15 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VI. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VI. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VI. Gun Purchase and Campus Gun Policies, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VI. Gun Purchase and Campus Policies, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 23 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler Johnston, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, undated. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler-Johnston Dormitory, 27 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler Johnston Hall, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler Johnston Hall, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler Johnston Hall, with edits/comments by Diane Strickland, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Double Murder at West Ambler Johnston Hall, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 30 July 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 9 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 10 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, with edits/comments by Marcus Martin, 13 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Chapter IX. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 14 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Chapter IX. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 14 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Chapter IX. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 14 August 2007, 5:50 p.m. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 14 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 17 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Mass Murder at Norris Hall, 22 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Emergency Medical Services Response, 1 August 2007. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Emergency Medical Services Response, 2 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Emergency Medical Services Response, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 5 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Emergency Medical Services Response, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 10 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IX. Emergency Medical Services Response, with edits/comments by Gordon Davies, 14 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IX. Emergency Medical Services Response, with edits/comments by Phil Schaenman, 17 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Emergency Medical Services Response, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 24 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IX. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, undated. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IX. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, undated. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter X. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, undated. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter VIII. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, with edits/comments by Phil Schaenman, 1 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter IX. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, with edits/comments by Mike Tierney, 9 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter X. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, 15 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Chapter X. Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, with edits/comments by Jim Kudla, 24 August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Draft, Appendix B - Interviewees, with edits/comments by Carroll Ann Ellis, 22 August 2009. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Appendix B - Individuals Interviewed by Research Panel, 22 August 2009. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Appendix B - Individuals Interviewed by Research Panel, 28 August 2007, 5:30 p.m. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Appendices, undated. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mental Health Commitment Process, 18 July 2007; reviewed with Panel on 24 July 2007 [RESTRICTED]. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence about Panel activities and update to families, June-August 2007. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Series II. Files of TriData, Subseries B. Confidential Seung Hui Cho Documents, 2007 (transmitted)., Extent: 0.53 cu. ft. (boxes 9-10)